happy employees are productive employees
but worries and uncertainties can take a
toll on them and personal safety is
usually among their concerns they worry
about how their families would cope
should anything happen to them is there
a way to help address this introducing
Sun life's group life insurance it's a
way of insuring several people under one
contract
[Music]
all at an affordable premium sonlife
group life insurance pays a benefit to
an employee's loved ones should he pass
away so no matter what happens his
family will have a brighter future the
coverage lasts for a year and may be
renewed easily with their family's
future protected your employees can face
each day with confidence keep their
focus
and rise to their full potential because
brighter lives lead to brighter Minds
bring peace of mind to both the company
and its members it won't take much to
embrace the program but the impact will
last a lifetime it all begins with Sun
Life Group Life Insurance brighter lives
brighter minds
talk to your son life adviser today
[Music]